gm-volt.com 2010-05-04

# Privacy Policy | GM-VOLT : Chevy Volt Electric Car Site

This is the web site of **GM-Volt.com.** It is wholly owned and operated by GM-Volt.com, LLC.  Lyle J. Dennis, M.D. is the founder, publisher and editor-in-chief.

We can be reached via e-mail at chevyvolt AT gmail DOT com.

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites.

You may choose to sign up on our unofficial Chevy Volt want list but there are no guarantees either real or perceived that that information can or will be used by GM or that it will offer you any opportunity to obtain a Chevrolet Volt.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

We are not responsible for accuracy of any information posted in our articles, comments or forum; they are all for entertainment only.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the email address above.

This Site contains links to web sites of third parties. GM-Volt.com, LLC is not responsible for the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their web sites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personal information. (Publisher) adheres to industry recognized standards to secure any personal information in our possession, and to secure it from unauthorized access and tampering. However, as is true with all online actions, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions of personal information, or other users of the Site may misuse or abuse your personal information that they may collect from the Site.

GM-Volt.com, LLC uses third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Site. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1×1 pixel .gifs or web beacons to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites, but will not collect any information which can personally identify you or can be linked to you. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, and the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes.

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site.

This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies’ privacy policies.
